let trivia = [
    {
        question: `Tarantino's films have identifying characteristics according to film critics. Which of these would NOT be one?`,
        choices: {
            a: `Ensemble casts`,
            b: `Non-linear time`,
            c: `Personification of animals and inanimate objects`,
            d: `Stylized violence`
        },
        answer: `c`,
        gif: `/assets/images/leocheer.gif`,
        wrong: `/assets/images/wrong1.gif`
    },
    {
        question: `What independent film that was directed, written, and acted in by Quentin Tarantino and was his first commercial success in 1992? `,
        choices: {
            a: `The Usual Suspects`,
            b: `In the Line of Fire`,
            c: `Untamed Heart`,
            d: `Reservoir Dogs`
        },
        answer: `d`,
        gif: `/assets/images/reservoirwink.gif`,
        wrong: `/assets/images/wrong2.gif`
    },
    {
        question: `Quentin Tarantino experiments with many genres of film. What genre did he pay homage with his 1995 film "Jackie Brown"?`,
        choices: {
            a: `Blaxploitation`,
            b: `Science fiction`,
            c: `Adult Western`,
            d: `Costume drama`
        },
        answer: `a`,
        gif: `/assets/images/jackie-brown.gif`,
        wrong: `/assets/images/wrong3.gif`
    },
    {
        question: `"Kill Bill" was released in two 'volumes' in 2003-04 due to its four hour running time. "The Bride" or "Black Mamba", portrayed by Uma Thurman, pursues "Bill" (David Carradine) to kill him. How does she accomplish this task? `,
        choices: {
            a: `Disemboweled him with a Samurai sword`,
            b: `Five point palm exploding heart technique`,
            c: `Forces him to commit Seppuku `,
            d: `Breaks his neck with a Okinawan numchuck`
        },
        answer: `b`,
        gif: `/assets/images/killbill-explodingheart.gif`,
        wrong: `/assets/images/wrong4.gif`
    },
    {
        question: `According to history Hitler died by suicide at a Berlin bunker. According to Quentin Tarantino in "Inglourious Basterds", how did he meet his demise?`,
        choices: {
            a: `Assassinated at Berchtesgaden along with his mistress Eva Braun`,
            b: `Killed by machine gun and explosions in a Paris theater`,
            c: `Leading an infantry charge at Stalingrad`,
            d: `Strangled by Mussolini in an argument`
        },
        answer: `b`,
        gif: `/assets/images/hitler.gif`,
        gif: `/assets/images/wrong5.gif`
    },
    {
        question: `Tarantino teamed with fellow director Robert Rodriguez to film a double feature that they called a __________ movie. `,
        choices: {
            a: `parody`,
            b: `homage`,
            c: `grindhouse`,
            d: `pastiche`
        },
        answer: `c`,
        gif: `/assets/images/grindhouse.gif`,
        wrong: `/assets/images/wrong6.gif`
    },
    {
        question: `What actor/actress received a pair of Academy Awards for appearing in two consecutive Quentin Tarantino films?`,
        choices: {
            a: `Samuel L. Jackson`,
            b: `Tim Roth`,
            c: `Uma Thurman`,
            d: `Christoph Waltz`
        },
        answer: `d`,
        gif: `/assets/images/bingo.gif`,
        wrong: `/assets/images/wrong7.gif`
    },
    {
        question: `In "Pulp Fiction", who shot Marvin in the face?`,
        choices: {
            a: `Jules Winnfield`,
            b: `Vincent Vega`,
            c: `Marcellus Wallace`,
            d: `Mia Wallace`
        },
        answer: `b`,
        gif: `/assets/images/pf-marvin.gif`,
        wrong: `/assets/images/wrong8.gif`
    },
    {
        question: `What two Tarantino movies are connected because of the Vega brothers, Vince and Vic?`,
        choices: {
            a: `"Reservoir Dogs" and "Pulp Fiction"`,
            b: `"True Romance" and "Pulp Fiction"`,
            c: `"Reservoir Dogs" and "Jackie Brown"`,
            d: `"From Dusk Till Dawn" and "True Romance"`
        },
        answer: `a`,
        gif: `/assets/images/vincentvega.gif`,
        wrong: `/assets/images/wrong9.gif`
    },
    {
        question: `Which Tarantino movie does Daryl Hannah appear in, where she uses a snake to kill someone?`,
        choices: {
            a: `Kill Bill Vol. 1`,
            b: `Inglorious Basterds`,
            c: `Kill Bill Vol. 2`,
            d: `Pulp Fiction`
        },
        answer: `c`,
        gif: `/assets/images/darylhannah.gif`,
        wrong: `/assets/images/wrong10.gif`
    }
];
